homedics.com 2018-03-19

# HoMedics.com | Privacy Policy

Protecting your privacy is important to HoMedics, LLC. We strive to keep your personal information confidential. By ensuring that you are aware of and understand the HoMedics, LLC Customer Privacy Policy, we can provide you with better service. Please take a moment to read the following policy to learn how we handle your personal information.

## Why we collect personal information

HoMedics, LLC collects and uses your personal information to give you superior customer service, to provide you with convenient access to our products and services, and to make a wider range available to you. In addition, we use your personal information to keep you up to date on the latest product announcements, promotions, special offers, and other information we think you'd like to hear about. From time to time, we may also use your personal information to contact you to participate in a market research survey, so that we can gauge customer satisfaction and develop better products. Moreover, we may collect your billing and shipping information for processing an online purchase.

## How we collect personal information

We collect information about you in several ways. For example, we ask for your contact information when you correspond with us or ask to be included in an email mailing list. We collect and store the information you provide in a secure database.

Our Ellia App requires that you allow us access to your camera and photos. The Ellia App captures an image and deletes the image captured within the amount of time it takes the App to recognize the color from your surroundings and match it to the mood light on your Ellia Aroma Diffuser, generally several seconds.

## When we disclose personal information

Your personal information may be shared with other HoMedics, LLC business units. They will protect your personal information in accordance with the HoMedics, LLC Customer Privacy Policy.

HoMedics, LLC also works with other companies that help us provide products and services to you, and we may provide your personal information to these companies. For example, we give shipping companies this information so they can deliver your refills or replacement products efficiently. The information they receive is for shipping and delivery purposes only, and we require that the companies safeguard your personal information in accordance with our policies.

HoMedics, LLC will not obtain your consent before disclosing your information to third parties.

At times we may be required by law or legal process to disclose your personal information. We may also disclose information about you if we believe that disclosure is necessary for the public interest.

## How we protect your personal information

HoMedics, LLC places safeguards to protect against the loss, misuse, unauthorized access and alteration of the data you send us with physical, electronic, and managerial procedures. We urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet.

Our website uses Secure Sockets Layering (SSL) to encrypt your personal credit information, including your credit card number, before it travels over the Internet. SSL technology is the industry standard for secure online transactions.

## Access to your personal information

You always have access to the information we have about you. If you would like to review other personal information that HoMedics, LLC may have about you, email us at privacy@homedics.com.

## Collecting other personal information

When you browse the HoMedics, LLC web site, you are able to do so anonymously. Generally, we don't collect personal information when you browse - not even your email address. Your browser, however, does automatically tell us the type of computer and operating system you are using.

Like many web sites, the HoMedics, LLC web site uses "cookie" technology. When you first connect to our site, the cookie identifies your browser with a unique, random number. The cookies we use do not reveal any personal information about you. Cookies help us understand which parts of our web sites are the most popular, where our visitors are going, and how long they spend there. We use cookies to study traffic patterns on our site so we can make the site even better.

In some of our email to you, we use a "click-through URL." When you click one of these URLs, you pass through our web server before arriving at the website that is your destination. We track click-throughs to help us determine your interest in particular topics and measure the effectiveness of our customer communications.

## Our company-wide commitment to privacy

To make sure your personal information remains confidential, we communicate these privacy guidelines to every HoMedics, LLC employee. HoMedics, LLC does not knowingly solicit personal information from children or send them requests for personal information.

If we are going to use your personal information differently from that stated at the time of collection, we will try to contact you via email using the most recent information we have. If you have not given us permission to communicate with you, you will not be contacted, nor will we use your personal information in a new manner.

The HoMedics, LLC Customer Privacy Policy is subject to change at any time. We encourage you to review the privacy policy regularly for any changes.

Please contact privacy@homedics.com to report any known or suspected privacy or security breaches or to submit privacy-related questions or complaints about privacy.

©2017 HoMedics, LLC. All Rights Reserved.

Last updated February 3, 2017
